reasons and excuses some of them credible some utter rubbish there's an interesting one that we
saw very recently in a secret report of the state department i want to tell you about that one
so you can reflect on that one that secret report made this point that grenada is different to
cuba and nicaragua and the grenada revolution is in one sense even worse i'm using their language
than the cuban and nicaraguan revolutions because the people of grenada and the leadership of
speaks english and therefore can communicate directly to the people of the same report also
said and said that also made us very dangerous and that is that the people of grenada and the
leadership of grenada are predominantly black they said that 95 percent of our population is black
and they had a correct statistic and if we have 95 percent of predominantly african origin of our
country then we can have a dangerous appeal to 30 million black people in the united states
the
way
this is
someопs
the
screw
this is
the